Rujhan Bin Munawwaruzzaman

Student In Dongyang Mirae University

Address Seoul, South Korea 08223

Phone +821075606191

E-mail rujhanmunawwaruzzaman@gmail.com

WWW https://bold.pro/my/rujhanbin-munawwaruzzaman-230609152930/207

Effective Student committed to learning, developing skills in Computer Software and team contribution. Self-directed and energetic with superior performance in both autonomous or collaborative environments working independently and collaborating with others on group projects. Motivated individual with strong work ethic and working independently. Strong organizational and team collaboration skills with experience in improving processes.

Skills

Teamwork and Collaboration

Testing and debugging

Analytical and Critical Thinking

Bilingual in Malay and English



Very Good







Work History

2021-11 - 2021-12

Retail Worker

Malaysian Restaurant, London

- Operated register to process payments and collect cash payment for order totals.
- Trained new employees by demonstrating tasks and coaching during daily activities.
- Upsold high-profit items such as appetizers and mixed drinks to enhance sales numbers.
- Worked closely with shift manager to solve problems and handle customer concerns.

2017-07 - 2017-11

Volunteer

Soy Bean stall, Selangor

- Maintained clean, neat, and operational facilities to serve program needs.
- Supported engaging, fun, and smooth-running events by helping with organization and planning.
- Gained operational knowledge and supported departmental needs.

Education

2022-02 - Current Bachelor of Science: Computer Software

Dongyang Mirae University - Seoul, South Korea

- Member of Malaysia-Korea Students Organization
- Received TOPIK scholarship (Test of Proficiency in Korean)

2021-07 - 2022-11

Associate of Science: Foundation in Science And Technology

University of Kuala Lumpur - Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Dean's List for 3 semesters (1.5 years) with CGPA of 3.82
- Graduated with TOPIK (Test of Proficiency in Korean) Level 3

Accomplishments

- Vice President in High School Council.
- Trifecta Tribe for Spartan race in 2018.

Languages

Malay Language

English Language

Very Good

Korean Language

Very Good

Arabic Language

Good